Marco Sousa

London, UK / immarco.com / sousa.marco@gmail.com

I am a passionate product designer, with over 8 years of experience in all sides of the industry. After a classic web design background, I quickly moved my focus to native mobile app design when the first iPhone launched in 2007. Since then, I have lead research, design and testing on multiple consumer and business products, over several industries, including transport, financial services, media, and retail.

EXPERIENCE

► The App Business · London, UK

Senior Product Designer

December 2014 - Present

Product Designer

April 2013 - December 2014

► Tuenti ∘ Madrid, Spain

Visual Designer

November 2011 - April 2013

▶ WePay ∘ Porto, Portugal

Web Designer (Remote Contract)

June 2011 - October 2011

► Freelance · Porto, Portugal

Web and App Designer (Contract)

September 2010 - October 2011

► CoreCreations • Porto, Portugal

Co-founder & Web designer

January 2008 - May 2010

SELECTED CLIENTS

ING

Transport for London

Unilever

Ford

News UK

EDUCATION

Professional Web Design

Flag (Porto, Portugal) - 2009 to 2010

Computer Science

ISEP (Porto, Portugal) - 2005 to 2009

SKILLS

User Experience Design User Interface Design User Research Native App Design Interaction Design

Product Strategy

SOCIAL MEDIA

twitter.com/h1brd
dribbble.com/h1brd
medium.com/@immarco